Let's have a duel, Akagami!
和我一決勝負吧 赤神
Sis Yuzuki and Sis Tsukuyo have already fallen for you.
結月姐和月夜姐已經被你攻陷了
What?
什麼
Now, I will have to save this temple!
現在將由我來拯救這所寺廟
Mia, you must be misunderstanding.
米亞 妳是不是誤會什麼了
Don't worry.
你們放心吧
At this point, I won't ask Akagami to get out anymore.
事到如今 我不會再說 讓赤神滾出去那種話了
If Akagami loses in the duel with me,
如果赤神在和我的對決中輸了
let's castrate him right away.
我們就立刻就把他閹了吧
Ca-castrate?
閹…閹了嗎
Is that even an option?
原來還有這種方法啊
Eh, you agreed?
咦 你居然願意嗎
WORLDLY DESIRES
(世俗雜念)
(TenPuru -No one can live on loneliness-)
《妙廟美少女》
(Episode 3: Let's Castrate Him) Akagami, watch the house please.
(第三話 把他閹了吧) 赤神 那就拜託你看家了哦
Understood.
我知道了
Be nice to Mia.
你要和米亞好好相處哦
What does "castrate" mean?
那個 閹了是什麼意思
Kurage, you don't need to understand it.
海月 妳可以不用懂的
You can just communicate with Mia with your fists.
你只要和米亞用拳頭交流一下 就沒問題了哦
Understood.
收到
We're leaving.
我們出門啦
Take care.
路上小心
Akagami,
赤神
are you mentally prepared?
你做好心理準備了吧
Yes, Miss Mia.
是的 米亞小姐
Calling me by my first name right off the bat.
馬上就直呼我的名字了嗎
You are not shy, are you?
你這男人可真會裝熟啊
I am Mia Christoph.
我是米亞克莉絲多夫
I moved into this temple before you,
是比你更早住進這所寺廟的前輩
so show me some respect.
所以你給我放尊敬點
Aren't you the same as me?
那妳不就和我一樣嗎
The same as you?
什麼和你一樣
You're really rude!
你可真是失禮啊
-I moved in here -I am Kagura.
-我是為了認真 -我是神樂
-to study Japanese culture… -Nice to meet you.
-學習日本文化才努力… -您好您好
Listen to me!
你給我認真聽啦
I moved in with her.
我是陪她一起過來寄宿的
Are you Mia's sister?
您是米亞的姐妹嗎
I'm her big sister.
我是她姐姐
What sister? And I'm older than you!
我們才不是姊妹咧 而且我年紀比你大吧
By the way, Miss Mia,
話說回來 米亞小姐
can we not have a duel?
我們可不可以不要一決勝負了
What? Are you messing with me?
什麼 你是不是瞧不起我啊
Don't tell me you forgot
第一次見面時你就非禮我
what you did to me when we first met!
我可不准你說忘了
I hate you the most!
我最討厭你了
So I must castrate you!
所以我一定要閹了你
What I did to you
第一次見面時
when we first met?
就非禮妳嗎
Well…
那個…
What's this?
這是什麼
This is Hyakunin Isshu.
是百人一首哦
In the past,
在過去
a samurai would choose one person's head as a sacrifice
武士為了拯救一百個人的性命
THE SAMURAI to save the lives of a hundred people.
(武士) 會選擇一個人的首級當作祭品
This is the duel to decide whom to sacrifice.
這就是決定要取誰首級的那場決鬥
Hyakunin Isshu.
百人一首
This is a national skill of Japan.
這可是日本的國技
Not the Japan I know.
這可不是我所認識的日本
So, let's begin.
那麼 開始吧
This thing,
這東西
is real.
她是來真的啊
Quickly, get into position.
你快擺好架勢吧
My next strike will cut you.
下次我真的會砍中的
This is bad.
不妙啊
But I can't hurt Miss Mia.
但是我又不能傷到米亞小姐…
Take this, Akagami.
接招吧 赤神
Secret Technique: Bare Hands Block the Blade!
秘技 空手接白刃
ABSOLUTE ROOKIE
(外行人)
Eh?
咦
Oh well.
哎呀哎呀
Her breasts
她的胸
popped out?
居然彈出來了
Don't look!
不准看
Namu sanbou!
南無三寶
Did I catch it?
我接住了嗎
These are
這是…
such beautiful breasts.
何等的美乳
Miss Mia!
米亞小姐
Oh dear.
哎呀呀
So the one who is to be punished
所以說
in the punishment game will be Mia.
懲罰遊戲就決定懲罰米亞囉
Mia is so weak.
米亞真是菜呀
It's all because of
這都是因為
the chest wrap.
裹胸布…
Come on, Akagami,
來吧 赤神
you decide the punishment.
就由你來決定懲罰的內容吧
Should I?
由我來決定嗎
Then let me decide.
那還是由我來決定吧
COMPLETE ASCETIC PRACTICES
(《苦行全集》)
This book contains all the ascetic practices that ever existed.
這本書包含了古今中外所有的苦行
Choose one ascetic practice
我們就從這本珍貴的《苦行全集》中
from this precious book.
選擇一個苦行來懲罰吧
Complete Ascetic Practices?
是《苦行全集》
COMPLETE ASCETIC PRACTICES Look at this "Suffocating Ascetic Practice".
(《苦行全集》) 看這個悶絕苦行
The ascetic practice of
這是將全身所有孔洞
blocking all the holes in the body and enduring it.
全部堵住並且忍耐的一種苦行
-Whole body? -Yes.
-全身… -是的
-All kinds of holes?
-各種洞
-I'll do it! -Don't!
-那我就做了 -還是算了吧
You don't have to pity me.
你不用同情我
Please calm down.
請妳冷靜一下
There's something I want more than that.
比起那個 我有個更想要的東西
What is it?
什麼啊
What I want
我想要的東西
COMPLETE ASCETIC PRACTICES is that.
(《苦行全集》) 就是那個
BREASTS You want this?
(胸部) 你想要這個嗎
Your purpose is indeed lewd.
你果然是以色色為目的…
It's okay. I won't mess around!
沒關係 我不會亂來的
-But… -Please, just for one night!
-但是… -拜託妳了 就算只有一晚也好
Wait…how can you…
等…怎麼這樣…
I want to try all sorts of things!
因為我想做各式各樣的嘗試
Try? Try what?
什麼嘗試 你想嘗試什麼
At least let me have a look!
最起碼讓我看一眼嘛
I'm not doing that!
誰會讓你看啊
You breast-assaulting maniac!
你這個胸部魔人
Oh dear.
哎呀哎呀
In the end,
最終
I couldn't reconcile with Mia.
我也沒能和米亞小姐和解
I want it so badly.
我好想要啊
Complete Ascetic Practices.
《苦行全集》
COMPLETE ASCETIC PRACTICES
(《苦行全集》)
There must be enlightenment tips in that book.
那本書裡一定有開悟的提示
I'm here to end things.
我是來做個了斷的
Miss Mia.
米亞小姐…
Just for one night.
只有一晚哦
Let's start the punishment game.
我們開始懲罰遊戲吧
Huh? What's happening?
呃 這是什麼情況
You look like you want to
我先前那樣感覺就像是
run away.
在逃避似的
So,
所以
I'll let you see.
來吧
You can do whatever you want.
你想怎樣就怎樣吧
Hurry up. I feel embarrassed too.
快點呀 我也是很害羞的
You want it, don't you?
你很想要吧
It's okay,
沒關係的
because
因為
this is just
這只是
a wet dream.
春宵一夢而已
A dream?
夢嗎
I see. It's a dream.
這樣啊 這是夢啊
So,
那麼…
no one is watching.
反正也沒有人在看
Miss Kagura?
神樂小姐
KEEP GOING. GO! TOWARD A MORNING KISS.
(繼續挺進 GO! 向著晨吻路線)
I'm not dreaming!
原來這是現實啊
Miss Mia, why are you doing this?
米亞小姐 妳為什麼要做這種事
You dare to ask why?
你竟然問我為什麼
It's because of the punishment game.
原來是懲罰遊戲
Definitely. I understand!
我懂了 我開悟了
This is wrong!
妳這樣做是不對的
KEEP GOING. GO! TOWARD A MORNING KISS. I understand.
(繼續挺進 GO! 向著晨吻路線) 我明白
You don't want to give up on Complete Ascetic Practices.
妳不想放棄《苦行全集》的決心
KEEP GOING. GO! TOWARD A MORNING KISS. But you can't sacrifice yourself
(繼續挺進 GO! 向著晨吻路線) 但是妳也不能為了那本書
for that book!
就獻出妳的貞操啊
Although the value of that book is indeed immeasurable!
雖然那本書的價值確實無從衡量
Akagami, what you want is… the book?
赤神 你想要的東西是…書嗎
Mhm, yes!
沒錯 就是書
So, Miss Mia, please don't do something that betrays yourself.
所以 米亞小姐 請妳不要做出這種背叛自己的行為
Go away!
討厭
Oh dear, the reconciliation failed again.
哎呀哎呀 和解再次失敗了呢
My mistake! This is my biggest mistake!
失策 失策 這真是我最大的失策
I misinterpreted his intentions.
我竟然會錯意了
I made things worse!
而且我還做了那麼丟臉的事
Why is there a man in the nunnery after all?
而且 為什麼尼姑庵會有男人啊
I should lock myself in the warehouse and meditate for a while.
我還是把自己關在倉庫裡 冥想一陣子吧
-Hello. -Why is it you again?
-妳好 -怎麼又是你
Miss Kagura told me to come over first.
神樂小姐叫我來追妳
Kagura!
神樂啊啊啊
Why are you here?
妳為什麼會來這裡呢
What does it have to do with you?
這和你有什麼關係
Eh… no way!
咦…咦…不會吧
The door won't open.
門打不開了
It seems that we can't get out through the window either.
好像也沒辦法從窗戶翻出去呢
There's no cell phone, and even if we shout loudly,
身上也沒有手機 而且就算我們大聲呼喊
people outside can't hear us.
外面的人也聽不見
Maybe it'll be just the two of us until morning.
也許我們只能兩人獨處到天亮了
Can you stay away from me?
你能不能離我遠點
I found a blanket.
我找到了一條毯子
-It's cold… -I don't want something touched by a man.
-畢竟現在很冷… -我不想碰被男人碰過的東西
I'll just leave it here then.
那我就放在這裡了
Here's a very strange table.
有一張很奇怪的桌子
Miss Mia, what is this?
米亞小姐 這個是什麼
Why should I answer your question?
為什麼我非得回答你的問題不可
This is called a sutra-writing desk.
這個叫做抄經桌
It is used to place the heads of those who have strayed from the Buddha's path for public display.
是用來放置 背離佛道之人的首級予以示眾的
Heads?
放首級嗎
That's what Kagura told me.
神樂是這麼告訴我的
Your head will be put on it sooner or later.
你的頭早晚也會被放上去的
You came into the temple without knowing this?
你連這個都不知道就進來寺廟裡了嗎
I'll give you the blanket.
我還是給妳毛毯吧
I said I don't want it!
我都說了不要了
The temperature will drop at night.
晚上氣溫會變得很低
-Stay away! -You'll catch a cold.
-別過來 -妳會感冒的
Don't be stubborn.
別逞強了
I said no!
我都說了不行…
If you keep coming closer,
你再繼續靠近的話
I'm going to get aroused!
我就要發情了
(TenPuru -No one can live on loneliness-) NO RISK, NO REWARD.
(妙廟美少女 不入虎穴焉得虎子)
Aroused?
發情嗎
No…no.
不…不是
It's not like that.
不是 不是這樣的
What are you doing?
你幹什麼
You'll catch a cold.
妳會著涼的
You should stop being so nice to me.
你還是不要對我這麼溫柔了
Can you forget about what just happened?
剛剛的事情你能把它忘掉嗎
And also what happened in your room.
還有在你房間裡發生的事情
Let's just pretend none of it happened.
你全都當做沒發生過吧
Forgetting about that
讓我把那些都忘記
is somewhat difficult.
確實有點困難
Even if you have to tell a lie,
這時候就算是開玩笑
at least tell me you'll forget it.
你好歹也說句我會忘記嘛
Just now,
剛剛的妳
you seemed a bit unlike yourself.
變得有點不像妳了
Unlike myself?
不像我嗎
Do you have some secrets?
難道妳是有什麼隱情嗎
There is no secret.
才沒有什麼隱情
That is the real me.
那就是真實的我
That's something that's been haunting me like a curse
那是從我懂事起
since I became self-aware,
就一直像詛咒一樣糾纏著我的
my nature.
我的本性
That's why I came to Japan.
所以我才會來到日本
That's the reason you came to Japan?
那就是妳來日本的理由嗎
Yes.
嗯
If possible, I hope you can forget about this too.
如果可以的話 我也希望你能忘掉這件事
My family
我家呢
is known as the "erotic family".
被別人叫做好色家族
Our family has been prestigious since ancient times.
我們家族自古以來就是名門
Listen carefully, Mia!
聽好了 米亞
Women from the Christoph family
克莉絲多夫家的女性
must be the focus of attention.
必須是所有人目光的焦點
Yes, Mother!
是 母親
Especially the attention of handsome men!
尤其要成為帥哥們的焦點
Mother is so cool!
母親好帥
We're finally in primary school.
我們終於升到小學了
I'm so excited.
真令人興奮耶
Can we make a hundred friends?
我們能不能交到一百個朋友呢
I wonder.
就是說呀
Mia, are you nervous too?
米亞 妳也很緊張嗎
Yes.
嗯
Can I also have a hundred lovers
我能不能也像母親那樣
like my mother?
擁有一百個情人呢
Just like that, I was isolated.
然後我就這樣被孤立了
By the time I noticed something was off, it was too late.
當我發現不對勁時 早就已經太遲了
Everyone was avoiding me.
大家都在躲著我
What about having two boyfriends?
交兩個男朋友的話怎麼樣
So erotic.
好色情呀
What about flirting with boys?
那去找男生搭訕呢
Pillow talk!
枕邊密話
So erotic.
好色情呀
Maintaining healthy thoughts is really difficult.
思想健康還真是困難啊
Mia, do you know?
米亞 妳知道嗎
Zen Buddhism is very popular in Japan now,
現在日本的“禪”相當興盛哦
Zen Buddhism?
“禪”嗎
I'm quite interested in it.
而且我也很感興趣呢
MIKAZUKI TEMPLE After hearing Kagura's introduction,
(三日月寺) 聽了神樂的介紹
I thought, this is the place.
我不禁想就是這裡了
In Japan, the Christoph family is not known.
在日本 克莉絲多夫家並不為人所知
In this nunnery where there are no men,
那在這個男賓止步的尼姑庵里
I can certainly become a new self.
我一定能蛻變為 全新的自己
But your arrival annoyed me extremely.
但是 因為你來到這裡 害我煩惱得沒完沒了
Isn't this just like before?
這樣一來 不就和以前一樣了嗎
I was just joking.
我是開玩笑的
It's not your fault.
這不能怪你
Don't worry. I'll leave this place.
你放心吧 只要我離開這裡就好了
Why are you crying?
你幹嘛哭啊
Actually, my family is also like this.
其實我家也是
Your family is also like this?
你家也是這樣嗎
I didn't expect to meet someone with the same experience as me.
沒想到竟然有和我同樣遭遇的人
You've had it tough too.
你也很不容易啊
Yes.
嗯
What an amazing coincidence.
真是驚人的巧合
No, this is destiny!
不 這是命運啊
If it's with this person,
如果是和這個人的話
I…
我…
I really am forgetful.
我還真是不長記性啊
I'm getting aroused again.
我又在發情
I'm having delusions.
又在會錯意了
I must run away.
我必須要逃
Whether it's Akagami or the Christoph family,
不論是赤神還是克莉絲多夫家族
I can only keep running.
我只能一直逃下去
Let's fight together, Miss Mia!
我們一起戰鬥吧 米亞小姐
Having a companion gives me great confidence.
有了同伴讓我信心大增
Let's walk on the path to enlightenment together.
我們一起邁向開悟之路吧
I will definitely hinder your practice.
我肯定會妨礙你的修行的
What are you talking about? This is exactly what I want!
說什麼呢 這正合我意
It's easier for you to say that, but,
你說是這麼說
you're just craving for my body, aren't you?
其實你只是對我的身體感興趣吧
Yes!
對
No, after all, we are just companions in practice!
不是不是 說到底我們只是修行的同伴
Even if I get aroused again, you won't compromise?
就算我再次發情你也不會嚇到嗎
We have a common standpoint.
我們的立場是一致的
Yes, I won't compromise, either.
對喔 那我也不會再嚇到的
-Let's work hard together. -Sure!
-我們一起加油吧 -好
I'm here.
我來了唷
When did you come here?
妳什麼時候來的
-I've been here all along. -Then why didn't you save us?!
-我一直都在哦 -那妳倒是救救我們啊
Alright. You should have reconciled by now.
好啦好啦 你們應該也已經和解了
Then, how about…
那你們要不要
COMPLETE ASCETIC PRACTICES Practicing asceticism here until morning?
(《苦行全集》) 在這裡苦行到早上呢
Sounds good.
好呀
As long as I have companions,
不管是什麼樣的苦行 只要有同伴
no ascetic practice is too daunting.
我都不足為懼
-Keep it up! -He he ho!
-加油哦 -嘿嘿哦
Kagura? What are you…
神樂 妳在做什…
Akagami, a bit deeper.
赤神 再深一點
I'm going in, Miss Mia.
我要進去了哦 米亞小姐
Oh my, such ascetic practice.
哎呀 真是苦行呢
Move your hand a bit deeper.
你的手再往深處放一些
Alright, Miss Mia!
好 米亞小姐
Miss Mia, I touched all these places.
米亞小姐 有好多地方都碰到了
Hold on, Akagami.
要忍住啦 赤神
Ah, Miss Yuzuki.
啊 結月小姐
What's this?
這個是…
TWISTER GAME Twister.
(龍捲遊戲) 是扭扭樂
Men and women in tight clothes twist their bodies all night long.
男女穿著貼身衣服 將肉體反覆扭轉一整晚
All night long.
一整晚…
What are you doing?!
你們在幹嘛啊
IN REFLECTION
(反省中)
What happened?
發生什麼事了
Who knows.
誰知道
Are you mad?
妳生氣了嗎
I'm not.
我沒生氣呀
By the way, Yuzuki.
說起來 結月
Hmm?
什麼事
You seem quite relaxed.
妳看起來相當悠閒嘛
But the blind date you postponed due to various reasons,
但是妳那個 因為各種狀況而延期的相親
isn't it today?
不就是今天嗎
The existence of this temple is staked
這場相親不是事關重大嗎
on your blind date, right?
攸關這所寺廟的存亡
MIKAZUKI TEMPLE I'm going to be late.
(三日月寺) 我要遲到了
Where's the blind date?
相親的地點在哪
Ryūkoku Temple!
龍刻寺
Can we make it?
妳趕得上嗎
If we can catch the next bus!
如果能坐上下一趟公車的話就可以
Then let's hurry up!
那我們就快點吧
The problem is, I have to change into my kimono on the way!
問題是 我必須要在路上換好和服
I've worked with kimonos before!
我以前打工時 有幫忙換過和服
You've done that job?
你連那種打工都做過嗎
Can you notify the other party in advance that you might be late?
那個 妳能不能提前 通知對方妳可能會遲到呢
No way!
不行
This blind date must be perfect!
這次相親不能有一點差錯
Why is that?
這是什麼意思
Actually,
其實
we should've
我們本應該
moved out of this temple immediately.
立刻從這所寺廟裡搬出去的
My parents aren't here and the temple has no abbot.
因為我爸媽都不在 所以我家的寺廟沒有住持
Without an abbot, his family
住持不在的話 住持的家人
doesn't have the right to stay in the temple.
就沒有在寺廟裡居住的權利
Although Kiki is helping us now,
雖然現在有嬉嬉姐來幫我們
I can't ask her to stay here indefinitely.
但是我也不能麻煩人家 一直留在這裡
So as soon as I graduate from high school,
所以等我高中一畢業
this temple will be abandoned.
這所寺廟就要廢寺了
But if my blind date is successful,
但是如果我相親成功的話
it would be different if we could invite a new abbot.
能請來一個新的住持就不一樣了
Miss Yuzuki, are you going to marry someone you don't love
結月小姐 為了這所寺廟的存續
for the sake of the temple?
妳要和不喜歡的人結婚嗎
It's my decision!
這是我自己做的決定
I absolutely can't let this temple be destroyed!
我絕對不能讓這所寺廟被毀掉
We'll make it, definitely.
我們會趕上的 一定會
NO PARKING
(禁止停車)
I didn't make it.
還是沒趕上
It's too far. I can't possibly run all the way there.
距離太遠了 我總不能跑著過去呀
Miss Yuzuki!
結月小姐
I borrowed a motorcycle!
我借到機車了
How did you get it?
你是怎麼借來的
I'm going to speed up!
我要加速了
Will this work?
我們有辦法趕上嗎
When I worked part-time as a deliveryman,
我在做宅配的打工時
I memorized all the shortcuts in this area!
已經記下了這附近所有的近路
Akagami, who are you really?
赤神 你究竟是什麼人
Out of gas.
沒油了
BUS Is that a bus?
(公車) 那個是公車嗎
Really?
真的嗎
TRANSPORT COMPANY, BLACK SEABASS
(運輸公司 黑色公車)
I mixed up a bus with a truck.
我竟然能把貨車和公車給搞混
I'm so stupid.
我還真是蠢啊
Sis Yuzuki is stupid and introverted.
結月姐姐就是既蠢又悶騷
-The Miss Third in my mind, stop talking! -Useless and introverted.
-我腦中的三女小姐 妳不要再說了 -既廢柴又悶騷
That's not relevant to being introverted. Stop talking.
這和悶騷沒關係吧 妳別再說了
Sorry, Akagami.
抱歉 赤神
I had you running around for nothing.
虧你還特地幫我的忙
I still can't do it, can I?
我果然還是做不到嗎
I can't inherit this temple.
憑我繼承這所寺廟…
Miss Yuzuki,
結月小姐
isn't this a good time to change clothes?
這不是個換衣服的好時機嗎
Change here,
妳在這裡換好衣服
and we'll go out when it stops at the next traffic light.
在車等下一個紅綠燈時我們就出去吧
But…
但是…
After we go out, we'll borrow this truck.
出去後我們就借這輛貨車一用
Of course, I have driving experience too!
當然了 我也有駕駛經驗
Borrow a truck? How?
你要怎麼借這輛貨車
Just give him some money!
給他點錢就行了
You're already in debt.
你都已經欠債了耶
It's okay. It won't make a difference.
沒事啦 這又不會少一塊肉
But it will increase your debt, so I don't think you should do it.
你的債務會變多啦 這樣不行吧
I see.
我明白了
Alright! Let's change quickly
好 那我們就趕緊換上衣服
and break out!
然後破門而出吧
Understood.
收到
30 MINUTES BEFORE THE BLIND DATE I cannot give up!
(距離相親還剩30分鐘) 我絕對不會放棄
(Next Episode: Go Take A Shower First) This is bad.
(下集 你先去沖個澡吧) 不好了
What happened?
怎麼啦
-Sis Yuzuki…she… -Did she go for revenge?
-結月姐她…她… -她去報仇了嗎
No.
不是
-Lo…love… -Love hotel!
-愛…愛…愛情… -愛情旅館
That's right.
沒錯
That's terrible!
這不是很不妙嗎